<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FloodAid</string>
	<string name="termsOfUse">Your use of the FloodAid website (herein referred to as “the site”) acknowledges you have read the terms and conditions of use located below carefully before registering and using the site.  In using the FloodAid site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions as they appear from time to time.\n
	\nThe information contained and presented in the FloodAid site is essentially a compilation of user contributed materials and information updates.  Whilst all care has been taken to ensure its accuracy, no guarantee or warranty as to its completeness or correctness is provided.  The FloodAid site is not, and is not intended to be, emergency warning and advice.  It should not be used as a substitute for particular advice and official media releases from public and government organisations.\n
	\nPlease note that whilst all care has been taken by the developers of the FloodAid application in the preparation and presentation of the data and materials presented, no responsibility is taken for errors or omissions and details may be subject to change.  The developers is not liable for any loss or damage directly or indirectly resulting from any action taken or reliance made by you or any of the information or material presented in your use of the site.\n
	\nThe FloodAid website intents to be a portal of publicly available information relating to the 2011 floods in Australia, and a forum to enable users to request and provide voluntary assistance to one-another.  Any assistance provided by one user to another thought the FloodAid website is done through their own volition, and FloodAid does not take any responsibility for any loss or damage arising from the conduct of its users.\n
	\nUsers of the FloodAid website should not rely on statements or representations and the application should only be used as a guide only.  If you use or otherwise rely on any of the information contained within the application or within this material, you are responsible for ensuring by independent verification its accuracy or completeness.
	</string>
	<string name="thanksTo">Hugo Sterin
	\nRonald Nooij
	\nJacobien Carstens
	</string>
	<string name="apiUrl">http://dev.floodaid.com.au/api/</string>
</resources>
